A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1980
  - United States, 1980; 1980/200
    - Carnegie Foundation, 1980 (Reel 9, Frame 694)
    - Ca, 1980 (Reel 9, Frame 923)
    - Center for Public Resources, Inc. (H-R), 1980 (Reel 9, Frame 1014)
    - Center for Rural Development, Inc., 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 1)
    - Center (A-S), 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 71)
    - Center on Technology and Society (Voremberg, David), 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 158)
    - Center for Population Activities, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 258)
    - Chicago Urban League (Compton, James W.), 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 398)
    - Ce-Ch, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 409)
    - City University of New York (A-C), 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 598)
    - Ci, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 696)
    - Cl, 1980 (Reel 10, Frame 886)
    - Committee (P-S), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 1)
    - Commonwealth Fund (Moloney, Thomas W.), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 186)
    - Conservation Foundation (A-S), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 229)
    - Cornell University (F-S), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 301)
    - Council on Foundations (Bolling, Landrum R.), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 410)
    - Council (B-M), 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 539)
    - Couzens, Michael, 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 685)
    - Co, 1980 (Reel 11, Frame 951)
    - Cr - Cu, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 1)
    - Da - Di, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 59)
    - Do - Du, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 288)
    - Edelberg, Cynthia D., 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 341)
    - Ea - Ed, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 378)
    - Ef - Ey, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 627)
    - Fahs, Charles B., 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 809)
    - Fa - Fe, 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 845)
    - Ford Foundation (Agriculture), 1980 (Reel 12, Frame 955)
    - Ford Foundation (A-S), 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
    - Fi - Fo, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 222)
    - Fr - Fu, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 268)
    - Gallaudet College, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 325)
    - Ga - Gl, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 373)
    - Go - Gu, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 594)
    - Hampshire College, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 688)
    - Hanson, Haldore, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 735)
    - Hab-Han, 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 826)
    - Harvard University (Clinical Epidemiology), 1980 (Reel 13, Frame 970)
    - Harvard University (A-K), 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
    - Har - Haz, 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 204)
    - He - Hi, 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 364)
    - Howard University (H-S), 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 490)
    - Ho, 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 824)
    - Hu - Hy, 1980 (Reel 14, Frame 991)
    - Indochina Refugee Action Center, 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 1)
    - Institute for Advanced Study (Conference on Russian and Soviet Studies), 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 172)
    - Institute (A-S), 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 273)
    - International (A-H), 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 479)
    - I, 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 531)
    - Janssen Pharmaceutica, 1980 (Reel 15, Frame 965)
    - Jobs for Arizona Graduates, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - Ja-Jo, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 191)
    - Juniata College, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 418)
    - Ka, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 529)
    - Ke, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 621)
    - Ki-Ku, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 809)
    - La-Le, 1980 (Reel 16, Frame 988)
    - Li, 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - Lo - Lu, 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 195)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation (Tenant Management), 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 269)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (B-P), 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 433)
    - Ma, 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 472)
    - Media Associates, Inc., 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 684)
    - Mexican American Cultural Center, 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 846)
    - Mc - Me, 1980 (Reel 17, Frame 967)
    - Mi - Mu, 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Napper, Larry C., 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 342)
    - National Alliance of Business, 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 449)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (B-W), 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 777)
    - National Center for Economic Alternatives (Alperovitz, Gar), 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 824)
    - National Commission on Air Quality (Brady, Gordon L.), 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 924)
    - National Council for Children and Television, 1980 (Reel 18, Frame 1027)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - National (A-C), 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 100)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (D-J), 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 282)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, Lyman, Richard W. (January - July), 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 294)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, Lyman, Richard W. (August - October), 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 547)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, Lyman, Richard W. (Novemeber - December), 1980 (Reel 19, Frame 856)
    - National Humanities Center (Project 87), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - National (E-H), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 140)
    - National (I-P), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 280)
    - National Urban League, 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 499)
    - National Urban League (Supplementary Material), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 637)
    - National Urban League (C-W), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 943)
    - National (R-W), 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 954)
    - New Jersey Historical Commission, 1980 (Reel 20, Frame 1011)
    - New York City School Volunteer Program, Inc. (Jones, Mildred E.), 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Ne, 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 178)
    - Ni - No, 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 471)
    - OICs of America, Inc., 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 628)
    - Organization of American States (Jacobson, Herbert L.), 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 712)
    - Organization of American States, Jacobson, Herbert L. (Supplementary Material), 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 767)
    - Our Lady of the Lake University, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - O, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 98)
    - Pacific Gas and Electric Company (Willrich, Mason), 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 300)
    - Pa, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 359)
    - Pearlman, Judith, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 586)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 631)
    - Pe - Pf, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 650)
    - Ph - Pi, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 682)
    - Pl - Po, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 760)
    - Public Communications, Inc., 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 939)
    - Pr- Pu, 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 1063)
    - Princeton University (A-U), 1980 (Reel 22, Frame 848)
    - Queens College, New York (Ogautey-Kodjoe, W.), 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Ra, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 5)
    - Re, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 85)
    - Ri, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 207)
    - Robinson, Sandra R., 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 286)
    - Rockefeller, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 394)
    - Russell Sage Foundation (Gifford, Bernard R.), 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 457)
    - Ro - Ru, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 650)
    - S - Sc, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 830)
    - Se - Sh, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 976)
    - Si-Sn, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Social Science Research Council (Prewitt, Kenneth), 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 97)
    - Southern Agriculture Corporation, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 245)
    - Stanford University (F-R), 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 584)
    - State University of New York (M-W), 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 709)
    - State University of New York at Buffalo (F-P), 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 835)
    - State University of New York at Old Westbury, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 889)
    - So-St, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 966)
    - Su- Sy, 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Ta - Te, 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 128)
    - Town Meeting: Mississippi, 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 343)
    - Th - To, 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 477)
    - United States, Agriculture (B-T), 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 661)
    - United States, Labor (B-R), 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 845)
    - United States, States (A-S), 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 965)
    - United States (A-S), 1980 (Reel 25, Frame 1024)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights (B-H), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - United States Conference of Mayors, 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 126)
    - University (A), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 176)
    - University of California (A-W), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 242)
    - University of Chicago (J-S), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 471)
    - University (C-H), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 682)
    - University (I-L), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 790)
    - University (M), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 891)
    - University of North Carolina (B-P), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 984)
    - University (P-V), 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 1093)
    - University (W), 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - U, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 160)
    - V, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 195)
    - W-Wa, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 288)
    - We-Wh, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 417)
    - Wi, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 549)
    - World Education, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 898)
    - Wo-Wr, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - Yale-China Association, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 189)
    - Yale University (D-S), 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 260)
    - Young Men's and Young Women's Hebrew Association, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 280)
    - Y-Z, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 590)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1980; 1980/200.A
      - C-T, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 636)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1980; 1980/200.W
      - Clark Foundation, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 675)
  - Philippines, 1980; 1980/242
    - A-J, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 677)
    - University of the Philippines (H-R), 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 696)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/242.E
      - de Dios, Emmanuel S., 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 757)
  - Puerto Rico, 1980; 1980/243
    - Gonzalez Villamil, Jorge L., 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 789)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1980; 1980/272
    - A-B, 1980 (Reel 28, Frame 794)
    - C-G, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - H-N, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 272)
    - O, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 401)
    - P, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 565)
    - R-S, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 756)
    - T-W, 1980 (Reel 29, Frame 912)
  - South America, 1980; 1980/300
    - I-L, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
  - Argentina, 1980; 1980/301
    - C-P, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 44)
  - Brazil, 1980; 1980/305
    - A-L, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 66)
    - University (B-S), 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 172)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/305.E
      - C-M, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 229)
  - Chile, 1980; 1980/309
    - B-R, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 242)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/309.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 267)
    - Chile - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/309.E
      - Balmaceda, Jose P., 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 270)
  - Colombia, 1980; 1980/311
    - B-U, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 308)
  - Costa Rica, 1980; 1980/313
    - Organization of Tropical Sciences, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 354)
  - Ecuador, 1980; 1980/317
    - 317, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 367)
    - E-M, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 385)
  - Guatemala, 1980; 1980/319
    - Martinez G., Mario A., 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 428)
  - Haiti, 1980; 1980/320
    - Hudicourt, Edith, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 431)
  - Honduras, 1980; 1980/321
    - O-P, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 434)
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/321.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 440)
  - Mexico, 1980; 1980/323
    - A-V, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 481)
  - Paraguay, 1980; 1980/329
    - N-R, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 685)
  - Peru, 1980; 1980/331
    - G-S, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 704)
  - El Salvador, 1980; 1980/333
    - National Center of Productivity, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 712)
  - England, 1980; 1980/401
    - Amnesty International (Argentina Problem), 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 716)
    - B-H, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 804)
    - Minority Rights Group (Ashworth, Georgina), 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 934)
    - I-M, 1980 (Reel 30, Frame 1019)
    - Pioneer Health Center (Glenrothes Center), 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - O-U, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 194)
  - Scotland, 1980; 1980/405
    - F-U, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 315)
  - Australia, 1980; 1980/410
    - A-G, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 335)
  - New Zealand, 1980; 1980/418
    - University of Auckland (Scott, Ian), 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 434)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1980; 1980/420
    - A-C, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 440)
  - Canada, 1980; 1980/427
    - B-M, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 469)
    - P-U, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 614)
  - Jamaica, 1980; 1980/437
    Includes Caicos, Turks, and Caymen Islands
    - S-U, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 725)
  - Windward Islands, 1980; 1980/455
    Includes Dominica, Grenada, St. Lucia, and St. Vincent.
    - WINBAN Research Center (Edmunds, Joseph), 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 745)
  - Ceylon, 1980; 1980/462
    - A-S, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 794)
  - India, 1980; 1980/464
    - Institute for Social and Economic Change (Population), 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 883)
    - A-V, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 1001)
  - Malaysia, 1980; 1980/473
    - C-S, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 1048)
  - Africa, 1980; 1980/475
    - Association (A-F), 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 1055)
  - Kenya, 1980; 1980/476
    - C-T, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - University of Nairobi (I-O), 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 144)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/476.D
      - Livestock, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 206)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/476.E
      - Etyang, Martin N., 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 378)
  - East Africa Region, 1980; 1980/477
    - O-U, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 383)
  - Rhodesia, 1980; 1980/483
    - Beaumont, C., 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 432)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1980; 1980/489
    - B-N, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 435)
  - Uganda, 1980; 1980/492
    - B-O, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 502)
    - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/492.D
      - 492D, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 547)
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 578)
  - Sudan, 1980; 1980/494
    - Hussein, Mansour F., 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 871)
    - Sudan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/494.D
      - Food and Agricultural Policy, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 880)
  - West Africa, 1980; 1980/495
    - O-R, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 892)
  - Ghana, 1980; 1980/496
    - G-U, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 1000)
  - Nigeria, 1980; 1980/497
    - D-W, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 1013)
  - France, 1980; 1980/500
    - C-S, 1980 (Reel 32, Frame 1053)
  - China, 1980; 1980/601
    - B-T, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/601.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 54)
  - Taiwan, 1980; 1980/605
    - A-W, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 64)
  - Japan, 1980; 1980/609
    - I-T, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 84)
  - Thailand, 1980; 1980/617
    - A-U, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 97)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/617.E
      - Pongsrihadulchai, Apichart, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 202)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1980; 1980/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics), 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 228)
  - Holland, 1980; 1980/650
    - I-V, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 245)
  - Indonesia, 1980; 1980/652
    - G-S, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 301)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/652.E
      - Tambunan, Mangara, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 322)
  - Ethiopia, 1980; 1980/701
    - A-G, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 324)
  - Belgium, 1980; 1980/707
    - D-P, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 330)
  - Belgian Congo, 1980; 1980/709
    - B-W, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 358)
  - Yugoslavia, 1980; 1980/710
    - Fovica Vuckovic Museum of Autographs, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 389)
  - Germany, 1980; 1980/717
    - P-V, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 396)
  - Tanganyika, 1980; 1980/723
    - C-U, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 487)
  - Zambia, 1980; 1980/724
    - Diallo, Valfoulaye, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 510)
  - Greece, 1980; 1980/749
    - Flessas, Yiannis, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 519)
  - Hungary, 1980; 1980/750
    - H-K, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 523)
  - Italy, 1980; 1980/751
    - B-V, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 528)
  - Norway, 1980; 1980/767
    - Christian Michelsen Institute (F-M), 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 605)
  - Portugal, 1980; 1980/773
    - Wong, J., 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 645)
    - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/773.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 647)
  - Poland, 1980; 1980/789
    - Trabka, Jan, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 650)
  - Sweden, 1980; 1980/800
    - H-S, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 654)
    - Sweden - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/800.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 676)
  - Switzerland, 1980; 1980/803
    - C-S, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 723)
  - Turkey, 1980; 1980/805
    - D-M, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 741)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1980; 1980/805.D
      - Agriculture, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 857)
  - Egypt, 1980; 1980/812
    - Rifaat, M. A., 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 895)
  - Israel, 1980; 1980/825
    - B-T, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 908)
  - Lebanon, 1980; 1980/833
    - American University of Beirut, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 938)
  - Members and Meetings, 1980; 1980/903
    - B-W, 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 945)
  - Humanities, 1980/911
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/911.E
      - Apter, David E., 1980 (Reel 33, Frame 1131)
      - Bender, Thomas, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
      - Grob, Gerald N., 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 40)
      - Holton, Gerald, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 85)
      - Jacqueney, Theodore, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 127)
      - Kammen, Michael, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 182)
      - C-M, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 230)
      - Smith, David H., 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 444)
      - R-V, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 506)
  - Art History, 1980/925
    - Art History - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/925.E
      - B, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 590)
      - C-G, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 829)
      - J-P, 1980 (Reel 34, Frame 971)
      - Schwartz, Buky, 1980 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
      - Stephens, William R., 1980 (Reel 35, Frame 174)
      - S, 1980 (Reel 35, Frame 431)
      - W, 1980 (Reel 35, Frame 453)
  - Geographic Medicine, 1980/928
    - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, 1980; 1980/928.E
      - P-V, 1980 (Reel 35, Frame 534)